[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Black Sea city of Sukhumi is the capital of this republic that proclaimed its independence from Georgia in the 90s.", "correct_answer": "Abkhazia", "incorrect_answers": ["Ajaria", "Iberia", "Ossetia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The zebra shark is very small and gentle and can be kept close to other fish.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "An average man inhales about 56,000 liters of air per day.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the car Lara Croft drove in the 2003 movie Lara Croft Tomb Raider: The Cradle of Life.", "correct_answer": "Jeep Wrangler Rubicon", "incorrect_answers": ["Nissan Patrol", "Jeep Liberty", "Jeep Commander"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These two states have Miami Universities.", "correct_answer": "Florida and Ohio", "incorrect_answers": ["Florida and Georgia", "Florida and Alabama", "Florida and North Carolina"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the name of the Mozzarella cheese mean?", "correct_answer": "To cut", "incorrect_answers": ["To suck", "To kiss", "To milk"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Juustoleipa cheese, traditionally made from reindeer milk, is typical of which region in Europe?", "correct_answer": "Finland and Lapland", "incorrect_answers": ["France and Switzerland", "Bulgaria and Macedonia", "Italy and Switzerland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the flamboyant flower beetle, also known as striped love beetle, feed on?", "correct_answer": "Nectar", "incorrect_answers": ["Insects", "Blood", "Carrion"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which famous comedian played the role of Miracle Max in the movie The Princess Bride??", "correct_answer": "Billy Crystal", "incorrect_answers": ["Danny DeVito", "Rodney Dangerfield", "Steve Martin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which statement is true about the movie The Bourne Identity?", "correct_answer": "There are no opening credits.", "incorrect_answers": ["The movie takes place in flashbacks.", "The movies was rated R for its violence.", "The guards in the US Embassy scene were all top stuntmen."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This movie was directed by Martin Scorsese. It was nominated for several Academy Awards but received two thumbs down from Siskel and Ebert.", "correct_answer": "The Color of Money", "incorrect_answers": ["The Last Temptation of Christ", "New York Stories", "Wallstreet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the top prosecutor, before Jack McCoy got the first chair in the top cases on Law and Order?", "correct_answer": "Benjamin Stone", "incorrect_answers": ["Paul Moriarty", "Paul Robinette", "Bill Flynn"]}]